#### I'm

### Muhammad Zeeshan

contact.muhammad.zeeshan@gmail.com GitHub || LinkedIn (+92) 309-6035017 || Faisalabad, Pakistan

# **Professional Summary**

Experienced full-stack developer with two years of experience in the industry. Seeking to leverage high proficiency in **SQL**, **JavaScript** and **C#** in a full-time career as a software developer. I have a strong interest in **Artificial Intelligence** and **Blockchain**. I am eager to explore opportunities where I can contribute to projects and start learning and growing in the exciting realm of technology.

# **Experience**

APRIL 2022 - APRIL 2024

#### Full Stack Developer - SiftoWhiz, Faisalabad

- Developed apps to address problems within the company client's needs.
- Modifying and testing changes to previously developed programs.
- Overseeing the automated testing and providing feedback to management during the development process.
- Tech Stack (React, Angular, ASP.NET Core, SQL SERVER)

APRIL 2024 - PRESENT

#### Full Stack Developer - Freelancer, Remote

- Communications with clients.
- Understanding their problems.
- Building, testing, uploading and managing softwares.

## Education

2019 - 2023 - Obtained Marks - 3.71/4.00 (92.75%)

**BS Information Technology** - Govt. Graduate College Samanabad Faisalabad

## Skills

 $\label{thm:communication} Teamwork \ | \ Communication \ | \ Problem-solving \ | \ JavaScript \ | \ C\# \ | \ Sveltekit \ | \ Svelte \ | \ React \ | \ Angular \ | \ ASP.NET \ Core \ | \ Tailwind \ Css \ | \ Pocketbase \ | \ SQL \ server \ | \ Supabase \ | \ Git$ 

# **Projects**

• **Crowdfunding Web App** - reactjs, asp.net core and sql server

A campaigner can post and donors can support the campaigner. Admin can manage all users, transactions, campaigns.

• Online Notice Board Web App - svelte, sveltekit, pocketbase and tailwind css, daisyUi

Admin can publish notice for one specific class or whole department or for the whole college. Admin can manage users. Students can view notices, profiles and can message admin.

• **Expense Tracker** - svelte, tailwind css, and daisyUi

Easy and simple browser storage based web application. Hold your daily cash record without involving any third party.